{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098954273","data":{"timestamp":" 947098954272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-4.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098962410","data":{"timestamp":" 947098962409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098969814","data":{"timestamp":" 947098969813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098977253","data":{"timestamp":" 947098977253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098989794","data":{"timestamp":" 947098989794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098990425","data":{"timestamp":" 947098990424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098991220","data":{"timestamp":" 947098991219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098992379","data":{"timestamp":" 947098992379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANAISHI"," userResponse":" PANAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098992832","data":{"timestamp":" 947098992831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098993618","data":{"timestamp":" 947098993618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099003367","data":{"timestamp":" 947099003367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099007110","data":{"timestamp":" 947099007110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099007741","data":{"timestamp":" 947099007740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099007844","data":{"timestamp":" 947099007843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 0bc9498d-e432-4ce3-a935-1e97b422739c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099016381","data":{"timestamp":" 947099016381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f95ebf87-91d8-4692-86a7-007475237bc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099016605","data":{"timestamp":" 947099016605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f95ebf87-91d8-4692-86a7-007475237bc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099017570","data":{"timestamp":" 947099017569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f95ebf87-91d8-4692-86a7-007475237bc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099018212","data":{"timestamp":" 947099018212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f95ebf87-91d8-4692-86a7-007475237bc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099018300","data":{"timestamp":" 947099018300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f95ebf87-91d8-4692-86a7-007475237bc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099033449","data":{"timestamp":" 947099033449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_radhi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099034833","data":{"timestamp":" 947099034833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_radhi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dhi"," userResponse":" dhi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099038976","data":{"timestamp":" 947099038976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099042335","data":{"timestamp":" 947099042335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" nya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099047572","data":{"timestamp":" 947099047572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099053631","data":{"timestamp":" 947099053631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099055098","data":{"timestamp":" 947099055097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099058457","data":{"timestamp":" 947099058457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mende"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099059874","data":{"timestamp":" 947099059874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mende"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099076257","data":{"timestamp":" 947099076256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yangu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ya"," userResponse":" ya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099078698","data":{"timestamp":" 947099078697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yangu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099082782","data":{"timestamp":" 947099082782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099084300","data":{"timestamp":" 947099084300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099100566","data":{"timestamp":" 947099100565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fi"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099107152","data":{"timestamp":" 947099107151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" fi"," userResponse":" fi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099107760","data":{"timestamp":" 947099107760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099111722","data":{"timestamp":" 947099111722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_punda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099112187","data":{"timestamp":" 947099112187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_punda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099116758","data":{"timestamp":" 947099116758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099118326","data":{"timestamp":" 947099118326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099124101","data":{"timestamp":" 947099124101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ndege"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099129870","data":{"timestamp":" 947099129870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ndege"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099130854","data":{"timestamp":" 947099130854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ndege"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ge"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099132452","data":{"timestamp":" 947099132451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 06b6e4b7-6484-4658-a6a0-10d45b2b9ee1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ndege"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099155634","data":{"timestamp":" 947099155634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099156141","data":{"timestamp":" 947099156140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099164623","data":{"timestamp":" 947099164623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwe"," userResponse":" mwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099164971","data":{"timestamp":" 947099164971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099173402","data":{"timestamp":" 947099173402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lala"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099173809","data":{"timestamp":" 947099173809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lala"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099178288","data":{"timestamp":" 947099178288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099178661","data":{"timestamp":" 947099178661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngwa"," userResponse":" ngwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099181715","data":{"timestamp":" 947099181715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099182005","data":{"timestamp":" 947099182005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099182480","data":{"timestamp":" 947099182480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099186059","data":{"timestamp":" 947099186059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gari"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099186299","data":{"timestamp":" 947099186298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gari"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099190085","data":{"timestamp":" 947099190085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mende"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099190660","data":{"timestamp":" 947099190659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mende"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099197022","data":{"timestamp":" 947099197022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099197288","data":{"timestamp":" 947099197288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099207737","data":{"timestamp":" 947099207737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_swala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" swa"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099213597","data":{"timestamp":" 947099213597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_swala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" swa"," userResponse":" swa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099214147","data":{"timestamp":" 947099214146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_swala"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099236428","data":{"timestamp":" 947099236427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pacha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099236942","data":{"timestamp":" 947099236942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pacha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099239093","data":{"timestamp":" 947099239093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" d07d278b-183d-4610-90c3-2953ee82ca04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_pacha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099253861","data":{"timestamp":" 947099253861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyati"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" nya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099254268","data":{"timestamp":" 947099254268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyati"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099258164","data":{"timestamp":" 947099258163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099258587","data":{"timestamp":" 947099258587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099262791","data":{"timestamp":" 947099262791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fi"," userResponse":" fi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099263332","data":{"timestamp":" 947099263332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_fisi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099269287","data":{"timestamp":" 947099269287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_basi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099269986","data":{"timestamp":" 947099269985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_basi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099277583","data":{"timestamp":" 947099277583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jiwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099277990","data":{"timestamp":" 947099277990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jiwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" we"," userResponse":" we"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099284569","data":{"timestamp":" 947099284569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099290406","data":{"timestamp":" 947099290406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099291248","data":{"timestamp":" 947099291248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_omba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099305456","data":{"timestamp":" 947099305456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kula"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099306273","data":{"timestamp":" 947099306273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kula"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099310469","data":{"timestamp":" 947099310469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099310893","data":{"timestamp":" 947099310893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099315689","data":{"timestamp":" 947099315689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dogo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099316505","data":{"timestamp":" 947099316505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dogo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099330157","data":{"timestamp":" 947099330157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099335958","data":{"timestamp":" 947099335958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099338654","data":{"timestamp":" 947099338654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b0ff2816-2c22-4008-8bd6-950a6c0b2f8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_wali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099351895","data":{"timestamp":" 947099351895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099352151","data":{"timestamp":" 947099352151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099356931","data":{"timestamp":" 947099356931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099357321","data":{"timestamp":" 947099357321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099363806","data":{"timestamp":" 947099363805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pera"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099366086","data":{"timestamp":" 947099366086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pera"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099371331","data":{"timestamp":" 947099371331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jasho"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099371773","data":{"timestamp":" 947099371773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jasho"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sho"," userResponse":" sho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099385251","data":{"timestamp":" 947099385251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dobi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099392139","data":{"timestamp":" 947099392139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dobi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099392504","data":{"timestamp":" 947099392504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dobi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099396684","data":{"timestamp":" 947099396684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099396941","data":{"timestamp":" 947099396941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099402728","data":{"timestamp":" 947099402728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zizi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099403479","data":{"timestamp":" 947099403479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zizi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099407008","data":{"timestamp":" 947099407007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gogo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099407273","data":{"timestamp":" 947099407272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gogo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099411993","data":{"timestamp":" 947099411993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yangu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ya"," userResponse":" ya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099413897","data":{"timestamp":" 947099413897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yangu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099421894","data":{"timestamp":" 947099421894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099422217","data":{"timestamp":" 947099422216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099424521","data":{"timestamp":" 947099424521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" f2b89d8d-423c-4d83-9d6d-a2eaed570fd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099440146","data":{"timestamp":" 947099440146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_choo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099440511","data":{"timestamp":" 947099440511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_choo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099444465","data":{"timestamp":" 947099444465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099444781","data":{"timestamp":" 947099444781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099448376","data":{"timestamp":" 947099448376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099448658","data":{"timestamp":" 947099448658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099452805","data":{"timestamp":" 947099452805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_osha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099453420","data":{"timestamp":" 947099453420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_osha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sha"," userResponse":" sha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099457575","data":{"timestamp":" 947099457574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyumba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyu"," userResponse":" nyu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099457939","data":{"timestamp":" 947099457939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyumba"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099461559","data":{"timestamp":" 947099461559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pera"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099461842","data":{"timestamp":" 947099461842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pera"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099467871","data":{"timestamp":" 947099467871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_oa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099473524","data":{"timestamp":" 947099473524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_oa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099474192","data":{"timestamp":" 947099474191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_oa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099477587","data":{"timestamp":" 947099477587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lala"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099477877","data":{"timestamp":" 947099477877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lala"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099482355","data":{"timestamp":" 947099482355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tano"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099482697","data":{"timestamp":" 947099482697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tano"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" no"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099489060","data":{"timestamp":" 947099489060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099489302","data":{"timestamp":" 947099489302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099491637","data":{"timestamp":" 947099491636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" c0e668c4-c396-4f54-af97-383d3f4e29f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099505137","data":{"timestamp":" 947099505137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_meza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099505804","data":{"timestamp":" 947099505804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_meza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099510517","data":{"timestamp":" 947099510517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twi"," userResponse":" twi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099510891","data":{"timestamp":" 947099510891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_twiga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099514979","data":{"timestamp":" 947099514978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lala"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099515302","data":{"timestamp":" 947099515302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lala"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099518748","data":{"timestamp":" 947099518748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tano"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099518963","data":{"timestamp":" 947099518963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tano"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" no"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099521933","data":{"timestamp":" 947099521933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099522257","data":{"timestamp":" 947099522256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099525685","data":{"timestamp":" 947099525685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ya"," userResponse":" ya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099525943","data":{"timestamp":" 947099525942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099530229","data":{"timestamp":" 947099530229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_swala"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" swa"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099536074","data":{"timestamp":" 947099536074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_swala"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" swa"," userResponse":" swa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099537108","data":{"timestamp":" 947099537108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_swala"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099540279","data":{"timestamp":" 947099540279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pacha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099540719","data":{"timestamp":" 947099540719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pacha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099544099","data":{"timestamp":" 947099544099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099544497","data":{"timestamp":" 947099544497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099547892","data":{"timestamp":" 947099547892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099548275","data":{"timestamp":" 947099548274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099550656","data":{"timestamp":" 947099550655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 921bde0b-904d-4a83-897a-d3e0ff8cfaed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_bibi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099565507","data":{"timestamp":" 947099565507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099565853","data":{"timestamp":" 947099565853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099569707","data":{"timestamp":" 947099569707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_radhi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099570014","data":{"timestamp":" 947099570014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_radhi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dhi"," userResponse":" dhi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099572392","data":{"timestamp":" 947099572392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099572691","data":{"timestamp":" 947099572691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099576237","data":{"timestamp":" 947099576237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ndizi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099576694","data":{"timestamp":" 947099576694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ndizi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ndi"," userResponse":" ndi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099577736","data":{"timestamp":" 947099577736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ndizi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099599537","data":{"timestamp":" 947099599536"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jiko"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099599944","data":{"timestamp":" 947099599944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jiko"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099603447","data":{"timestamp":" 947099603447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwe"," userResponse":" mwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099603788","data":{"timestamp":" 947099603788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwembe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099607534","data":{"timestamp":" 947099607534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ona"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099613587","data":{"timestamp":" 947099613587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ona"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099614079","data":{"timestamp":" 947099614078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ona"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099621960","data":{"timestamp":" 947099621960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099622818","data":{"timestamp":" 947099622818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_visu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" su"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099626697","data":{"timestamp":" 947099626697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_babu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099627263","data":{"timestamp":" 947099627263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_babu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099632002","data":{"timestamp":" 947099632002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_rangi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099632859","data":{"timestamp":" 947099632859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_rangi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngi"," userResponse":" ngi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099634603","data":{"timestamp":" 947099634603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 46c5ccff-8ebe-404f-b9dc-2730dd3fd9fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_rangi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099648172","data":{"timestamp":" 947099648172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_oa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099648444","data":{"timestamp":" 947099648444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_oa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099651749","data":{"timestamp":" 947099651749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099652147","data":{"timestamp":" 947099652147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099653482","data":{"timestamp":" 947099653481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099656326","data":{"timestamp":" 947099656326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wavu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099657359","data":{"timestamp":" 947099657359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wavu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vu"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099660089","data":{"timestamp":" 947099660088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hoho"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099660604","data":{"timestamp":" 947099660603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hoho"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099664133","data":{"timestamp":" 947099664133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099664465","data":{"timestamp":" 947099664464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099668301","data":{"timestamp":" 947099668301"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099668551","data":{"timestamp":" 947099668551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099671898","data":{"timestamp":" 947099671898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gogo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099672146","data":{"timestamp":" 947099672145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gogo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099676009","data":{"timestamp":" 947099676008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zuri"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zu"," userResponse":" zu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099678535","data":{"timestamp":" 947099678534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zuri"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099682421","data":{"timestamp":" 947099682421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099682828","data":{"timestamp":" 947099682828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099683320","data":{"timestamp":" 947099683320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099684454","data":{"timestamp":" 947099684454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099692427","data":{"timestamp":" 947099692427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 8ff6df68-f977-4dc1-afc2-014e904930f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_jicho"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099703707","data":{"timestamp":" 947099703707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099704081","data":{"timestamp":" 947099704081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099704731","data":{"timestamp":" 947099704731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099704929","data":{"timestamp":" 947099704929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099705839","data":{"timestamp":" 947099705838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099719005","data":{"timestamp":" 947099719005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099720682","data":{"timestamp":" 947099720681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099723235","data":{"timestamp":" 947099723235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099724930","data":{"timestamp":" 947099724929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099726824","data":{"timestamp":" 947099726823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099728485","data":{"timestamp":" 947099728485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NICHAGUE"," userResponse":" NICHAGUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099729539","data":{"timestamp":" 947099729538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099731828","data":{"timestamp":" 947099731828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NICHAGUE"," userResponse":" NICHAGUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099734087","data":{"timestamp":" 947099734087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099736136","data":{"timestamp":" 947099736135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099737225","data":{"timestamp":" 947099737224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099737948","data":{"timestamp":" 947099737947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099739740","data":{"timestamp":" 947099739740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099741340","data":{"timestamp":" 947099741340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099742460","data":{"timestamp":" 947099742460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099744560","data":{"timestamp":" 947099744559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099745556","data":{"timestamp":" 947099745544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INARUKA"," userResponse":" INARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099746262","data":{"timestamp":" 947099746262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099747024","data":{"timestamp":" 947099747024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099749193","data":{"timestamp":" 947099749193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099749677","data":{"timestamp":" 947099749677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" INARUKA"," userResponse":" START_INARUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099750482","data":{"timestamp":" 947099750480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" INARUKA"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099752182","data":{"timestamp":" 947099752181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INARUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099752759","data":{"timestamp":" 947099752759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099753452","data":{"timestamp":" 947099753452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099753759","data":{"timestamp":" 947099753759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099755394","data":{"timestamp":" 947099755393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099756171","data":{"timestamp":" 947099756171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOGOPA"," userResponse":" NAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099756639","data":{"timestamp":" 947099756638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099758783","data":{"timestamp":" 947099758783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099759507","data":{"timestamp":" 947099759507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOGOPA"," userResponse":" NAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099767873","data":{"timestamp":" 947099767873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099771340","data":{"timestamp":" 947099771340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099772127","data":{"timestamp":" 947099772127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099773258","data":{"timestamp":" 947099773257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099774893","data":{"timestamp":" 947099774892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099775594","data":{"timestamp":" 947099775594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099776272","data":{"timestamp":" 947099776272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099778536","data":{"timestamp":" 947099778535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099779397","data":{"timestamp":" 947099779396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099779617","data":{"timestamp":" 947099779616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099779996","data":{"timestamp":" 947099779995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099780146","data":{"timestamp":" 947099780146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099780782","data":{"timestamp":" 947099780782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099782730","data":{"timestamp":" 947099782729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099784330","data":{"timestamp":" 947099784330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099784334","data":{"timestamp":" 947099784334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099784337","data":{"timestamp":" 947099784336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099784339","data":{"timestamp":" 947099784339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099785134","data":{"timestamp":" 947099785134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099787338","data":{"timestamp":" 947099787338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099788261","data":{"timestamp":" 947099788260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099789178","data":{"timestamp":" 947099789176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099789823","data":{"timestamp":" 947099789823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099789907","data":{"timestamp":" 947099789907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099790472","data":{"timestamp":" 947099790471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099795164","data":{"timestamp":" 947099795164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099796986","data":{"timestamp":" 947099796986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099797977","data":{"timestamp":" 947099797977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099797984","data":{"timestamp":" 947099797984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099798260","data":{"timestamp":" 947099798259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099800257","data":{"timestamp":" 947099800257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099802820","data":{"timestamp":" 947099802820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099803674","data":{"timestamp":" 947099803674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" STESHENI"," userResponse":" STESHENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099804107","data":{"timestamp":" 947099804107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099804767","data":{"timestamp":" 947099804766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099805330","data":{"timestamp":" 947099805330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099810338","data":{"timestamp":" 947099810338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099813027","data":{"timestamp":" 947099813027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" STESHENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099815068","data":{"timestamp":" 947099815068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099816938","data":{"timestamp":" 947099816938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099818821","data":{"timestamp":" 947099818821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099820959","data":{"timestamp":" 947099820959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITACHOKA"," userResponse":" NITACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099821792","data":{"timestamp":" 947099821792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099823812","data":{"timestamp":" 947099823812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITACHOKA"," userResponse":" NITACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099827258","data":{"timestamp":" 947099827258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099829358","data":{"timestamp":" 947099829358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099830530","data":{"timestamp":" 947099830530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099831304","data":{"timestamp":" 947099831304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099832971","data":{"timestamp":" 947099832971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099833893","data":{"timestamp":" 947099833892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099834623","data":{"timestamp":" 947099834622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099837011","data":{"timestamp":" 947099837011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099837445","data":{"timestamp":" 947099837445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099837829","data":{"timestamp":" 947099837829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099838262","data":{"timestamp":" 947099838262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099838706","data":{"timestamp":" 947099838706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099839421","data":{"timestamp":" 947099839421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099841338","data":{"timestamp":" 947099841337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099841963","data":{"timestamp":" 947099841963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099842310","data":{"timestamp":" 947099842309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099842938","data":{"timestamp":" 947099842938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099842941","data":{"timestamp":" 947099842941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099844520","data":{"timestamp":" 947099844520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099847004","data":{"timestamp":" 947099847003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099848103","data":{"timestamp":" 947099848103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099848488","data":{"timestamp":" 947099848488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099849441","data":{"timestamp":" 947099849441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099851866","data":{"timestamp":" 947099851866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099851868","data":{"timestamp":" 947099851868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099852359","data":{"timestamp":" 947099852359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099854676","data":{"timestamp":" 947099854675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099855425","data":{"timestamp":" 947099855425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" START_NITATUMIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099856977","data":{"timestamp":" 947099856977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099859463","data":{"timestamp":" 947099859462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099860313","data":{"timestamp":" 947099860312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099861265","data":{"timestamp":" 947099861265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099862202","data":{"timestamp":" 947099862202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099862305","data":{"timestamp":" 947099862305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099863028","data":{"timestamp":" 947099863028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" KUBEBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099863710","data":{"timestamp":" 947099863710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099864435","data":{"timestamp":" 947099864434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZITO"," userResponse":" MIZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099866887","data":{"timestamp":" 947099866887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099867470","data":{"timestamp":" 947099867470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099867889","data":{"timestamp":" 947099867889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099868589","data":{"timestamp":" 947099868589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099869194","data":{"timestamp":" 947099869194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099869933","data":{"timestamp":" 947099869932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099870217","data":{"timestamp":" 947099870217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099870635","data":{"timestamp":" 947099870635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" KUBEBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099871615","data":{"timestamp":" 947099871615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099872637","data":{"timestamp":" 947099872637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZITO"," userResponse":" MIZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099874832","data":{"timestamp":" 947099874832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099876199","data":{"timestamp":" 947099876197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099877016","data":{"timestamp":" 947099877015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099878233","data":{"timestamp":" 947099878232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099879803","data":{"timestamp":" 947099879802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099880910","data":{"timestamp":" 947099880910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099881978","data":{"timestamp":" 947099881978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099882923","data":{"timestamp":" 947099882923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099885339","data":{"timestamp":" 947099885338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099885886","data":{"timestamp":" 947099885885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099886206","data":{"timestamp":" 947099886206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099887172","data":{"timestamp":" 947099887172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATANIPATIA"," userResponse":" ATANIPATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099887955","data":{"timestamp":" 947099887955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099888561","data":{"timestamp":" 947099888559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099890606","data":{"timestamp":" 947099890606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099893015","data":{"timestamp":" 947099893015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099893501","data":{"timestamp":" 947099893501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099894294","data":{"timestamp":" 947099894294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ATANIPATIA"," userResponse":" START_ATANIPATIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099896397","data":{"timestamp":" 947099896397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ATANIPATIA"," userResponse":" START_ATANIPATIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099898498","data":{"timestamp":" 947099898498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATANIPATIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099900542","data":{"timestamp":" 947099900542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099900995","data":{"timestamp":" 947099900995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099903202","data":{"timestamp":" 947099903202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099903929","data":{"timestamp":" 947099903929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJARIBU"," userResponse":" NIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099904673","data":{"timestamp":" 947099904672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099904893","data":{"timestamp":" 947099904892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099905643","data":{"timestamp":" 947099905642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099908069","data":{"timestamp":" 947099908069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099908876","data":{"timestamp":" 947099908875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJARIBU"," userResponse":" NIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099909551","data":{"timestamp":" 947099909551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099909945","data":{"timestamp":" 947099909945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099910590","data":{"timestamp":" 947099910590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099912994","data":{"timestamp":" 947099912994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099913356","data":{"timestamp":" 947099913356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099914084","data":{"timestamp":" 947099914084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAMINI"," userResponse":" SIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099914673","data":{"timestamp":" 947099914673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099915264","data":{"timestamp":" 947099915264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099917046","data":{"timestamp":" 947099917046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099917586","data":{"timestamp":" 947099917586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099918134","data":{"timestamp":" 947099918134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAMINI"," userResponse":" SIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099918656","data":{"timestamp":" 947099918655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099919476","data":{"timestamp":" 947099919476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099921717","data":{"timestamp":" 947099921716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AAH"," userResponse":" AAH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099926053","data":{"timestamp":" 947099926053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AAH"," userResponse":" AAH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099927982","data":{"timestamp":" 947099927982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099929447","data":{"timestamp":" 947099929447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," userResponse":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099930564","data":{"timestamp":" 947099930564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099932625","data":{"timestamp":" 947099932625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," userResponse":" START_NITAKACHOTUMIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099933483","data":{"timestamp":" 947099933483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," userResponse":" START_NITAKACHOTUMIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099935461","data":{"timestamp":" 947099935460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099938068","data":{"timestamp":" 947099938068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099938758","data":{"timestamp":" 947099938757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099939850","data":{"timestamp":" 947099939845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099941675","data":{"timestamp":" 947099941675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" START_NITATUMIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099942461","data":{"timestamp":" 947099942461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" START_NITATUMIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099944302","data":{"timestamp":" 947099944302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099944763","data":{"timestamp":" 947099944763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099946472","data":{"timestamp":" 947099946471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099948488","data":{"timestamp":" 947099948486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099948582","data":{"timestamp":" 947099948582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099954712","data":{"timestamp":" 947099954711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099961734","data":{"timestamp":" 947099961734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099968373","data":{"timestamp":" 947099968373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" ce11838f-d341-45c1-bca4-5fecb6fb29c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099981307","data":{"timestamp":" 947099981306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 33ca475e-771f-46f0-b001-8c4c621bab4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099984256","data":{"timestamp":" 947099984256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 33ca475e-771f-46f0-b001-8c4c621bab4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099994698","data":{"timestamp":" 947099994697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099994931","data":{"timestamp":" 947099994931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099995374","data":{"timestamp":" 947099995374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099995578","data":{"timestamp":" 947099995578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099996322","data":{"timestamp":" 947099996321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947099999386","data":{"timestamp":" 947099999385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100000411","data":{"timestamp":" 947100000410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100001923","data":{"timestamp":" 947100001918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100003266","data":{"timestamp":" 947100003266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100004590","data":{"timestamp":" 947100004590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100005631","data":{"timestamp":" 947100005630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100007134","data":{"timestamp":" 947100007133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100008738","data":{"timestamp":" 947100008738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100015123","data":{"timestamp":" 947100015123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100017426","data":{"timestamp":" 947100017426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100018293","data":{"timestamp":" 947100018292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100018823","data":{"timestamp":" 947100018822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100019571","data":{"timestamp":" 947100019571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100019915","data":{"timestamp":" 947100019914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100021638","data":{"timestamp":" 947100021638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100022035","data":{"timestamp":" 947100022035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" START_ANARUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100023015","data":{"timestamp":" 947100023015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100024732","data":{"timestamp":" 947100024732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100025816","data":{"timestamp":" 947100025815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100026531","data":{"timestamp":" 947100026531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100028635","data":{"timestamp":" 947100028635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100030974","data":{"timestamp":" 947100030974"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100032160","data":{"timestamp":" 947100032159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100032634","data":{"timestamp":" 947100032634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100032875","data":{"timestamp":" 947100032875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100033638","data":{"timestamp":" 947100033638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100034060","data":{"timestamp":" 947100034059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100036137","data":{"timestamp":" 947100036137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100037235","data":{"timestamp":" 947100037235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100037840","data":{"timestamp":" 947100037840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100038138","data":{"timestamp":" 947100038138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100038741","data":{"timestamp":" 947100038741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100039369","data":{"timestamp":" 947100039369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100041732","data":{"timestamp":" 947100041731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100042367","data":{"timestamp":" 947100042367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100043190","data":{"timestamp":" 947100043190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100044026","data":{"timestamp":" 947100044026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100045902","data":{"timestamp":" 947100045902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100046398","data":{"timestamp":" 947100046398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100048355","data":{"timestamp":" 947100048355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100049963","data":{"timestamp":" 947100049963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100052344","data":{"timestamp":" 947100052344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100053362","data":{"timestamp":" 947100053361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" ANAWAAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100053966","data":{"timestamp":" 947100053966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100054535","data":{"timestamp":" 947100054534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100056308","data":{"timestamp":" 947100056308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100057237","data":{"timestamp":" 947100057237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" ANAWAAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100058567","data":{"timestamp":" 947100058567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100059380","data":{"timestamp":" 947100059380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100062394","data":{"timestamp":" 947100062394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100064656","data":{"timestamp":" 947100064655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100065523","data":{"timestamp":" 947100065523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100066144","data":{"timestamp":" 947100066143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOMBA"," userResponse":" VYOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100066987","data":{"timestamp":" 947100066987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100068672","data":{"timestamp":" 947100068672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100069367","data":{"timestamp":" 947100069366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100070136","data":{"timestamp":" 947100070136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOMBA"," userResponse":" VYOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100071488","data":{"timestamp":" 947100071488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100075341","data":{"timestamp":" 947100075340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100077644","data":{"timestamp":" 947100077644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100078776","data":{"timestamp":" 947100078776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANAANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100079860","data":{"timestamp":" 947100079859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAONI"," userResponse":" UBAONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100082036","data":{"timestamp":" 947100082036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100084333","data":{"timestamp":" 947100084333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANAANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100084741","data":{"timestamp":" 947100084741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAONI"," userResponse":" UBAONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100087382","data":{"timestamp":" 947100087382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100087742","data":{"timestamp":" 947100087742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100087859","data":{"timestamp":" 947100087859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" b59577e6-61fd-4d3e-a2e8-1e0b14346ee3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100098055","data":{"timestamp":" 947100098055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100098285","data":{"timestamp":" 947100098285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100099263","data":{"timestamp":" 947100099262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100100536","data":{"timestamp":" 947100100536"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100103475","data":{"timestamp":" 947100103475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100104333","data":{"timestamp":" 947100104332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100104654","data":{"timestamp":" 947100104654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100105887","data":{"timestamp":" 947100105887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100109325","data":{"timestamp":" 947100109325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100110310","data":{"timestamp":" 947100110310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100110563","data":{"timestamp":" 947100110563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100111507","data":{"timestamp":" 947100111506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100114335","data":{"timestamp":" 947100114335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100115368","data":{"timestamp":" 947100115368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100115840","data":{"timestamp":" 947100115840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100120350","data":{"timestamp":" 947100120350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100120427","data":{"timestamp":" 947100120427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100139283","data":{"timestamp":" 947100139283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100149542","data":{"timestamp":" 947100149542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 2f90fb68-4a96-495a-a4b0-39cbffd74372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100161567","data":{"timestamp":" 947100161564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100162059","data":{"timestamp":" 947100162059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100163203","data":{"timestamp":" 947100163202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" ANAFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100163584","data":{"timestamp":" 947100163584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100164239","data":{"timestamp":" 947100164239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100164632","data":{"timestamp":" 947100164632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100165377","data":{"timestamp":" 947100165377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGA"," userResponse":" MKONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100166168","data":{"timestamp":" 947100166168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100168862","data":{"timestamp":" 947100168861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100178715","data":{"timestamp":" 947100178715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100179991","data":{"timestamp":" 947100179991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" START_ANAFAHAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100182828","data":{"timestamp":" 947100182828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100184579","data":{"timestamp":" 947100184579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100185337","data":{"timestamp":" 947100185337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100186447","data":{"timestamp":" 947100186447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100186851","data":{"timestamp":" 947100186850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" START_TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100187688","data":{"timestamp":" 947100187688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" START_TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100189355","data":{"timestamp":" 947100189355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100190275","data":{"timestamp":" 947100190275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100191589","data":{"timestamp":" 947100191589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" MKONGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100192877","data":{"timestamp":" 947100192877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100193048","data":{"timestamp":" 947100193048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGA"," userResponse":" START_MREFU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100194436","data":{"timestamp":" 947100194436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGA"," userResponse":" MKONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100194948","data":{"timestamp":" 947100194947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100197355","data":{"timestamp":" 947100197355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100197862","data":{"timestamp":" 947100197859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100198145","data":{"timestamp":" 947100198145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100198618","data":{"timestamp":" 947100198618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100199343","data":{"timestamp":" 947100199343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100200050","data":{"timestamp":" 947100200050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100200854","data":{"timestamp":" 947100200854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100201549","data":{"timestamp":" 947100201549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100201815","data":{"timestamp":" 947100201815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100202439","data":{"timestamp":" 947100202438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100204364","data":{"timestamp":" 947100204364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100208981","data":{"timestamp":" 947100208981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100211874","data":{"timestamp":" 947100211874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100215466","data":{"timestamp":" 947100215465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100223754","data":{"timestamp":" 947100223754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100225916","data":{"timestamp":" 947100225916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100229038","data":{"timestamp":" 947100229037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100238095","data":{"timestamp":" 947100238095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100243352","data":{"timestamp":" 947100243352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100245819","data":{"timestamp":" 947100245819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100247476","data":{"timestamp":" 947100247476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100253402","data":{"timestamp":" 947100253402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100254825","data":{"timestamp":" 947100254825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100257408","data":{"timestamp":" 947100257408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100259456","data":{"timestamp":" 947100259456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100259910","data":{"timestamp":" 947100259910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100260673","data":{"timestamp":" 947100260673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100261955","data":{"timestamp":" 947100261954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOWEKWA"," userResponse":" KILICHOWEKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100263014","data":{"timestamp":" 947100263011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100263259","data":{"timestamp":" 947100263259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100263682","data":{"timestamp":" 947100263682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100264278","data":{"timestamp":" 947100264277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100267003","data":{"timestamp":" 947100267003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100268832","data":{"timestamp":" 947100268832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100271579","data":{"timestamp":" 947100271579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100274571","data":{"timestamp":" 947100274571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOWEKWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100277684","data":{"timestamp":" 947100277684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100281626","data":{"timestamp":" 947100281625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100283602","data":{"timestamp":" 947100283602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100285848","data":{"timestamp":" 947100285848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100288096","data":{"timestamp":" 947100288096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100288600","data":{"timestamp":" 947100288600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100289203","data":{"timestamp":" 947100289203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100290076","data":{"timestamp":" 947100290076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAZAA"," userResponse":" AKAZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100290899","data":{"timestamp":" 947100290899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100291847","data":{"timestamp":" 947100291846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100292788","data":{"timestamp":" 947100292787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDADISI"," userResponse":" MDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100295583","data":{"timestamp":" 947100295583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100296855","data":{"timestamp":" 947100296854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100298737","data":{"timestamp":" 947100298737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100300816","data":{"timestamp":" 947100300816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAZAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100302934","data":{"timestamp":" 947100302934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100305157","data":{"timestamp":" 947100305157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100308070","data":{"timestamp":" 947100308069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDADISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100311876","data":{"timestamp":" 947100311876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100312040","data":{"timestamp":" 947100312040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100312489","data":{"timestamp":" 947100312489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALI"," userResponse":" SWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100312710","data":{"timestamp":" 947100312710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100313191","data":{"timestamp":" 947100313191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100313864","data":{"timestamp":" 947100313863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMA"," userResponse":" MNYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100315133","data":{"timestamp":" 947100315133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMUONA"," userResponse":" ALIYEMUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100319956","data":{"timestamp":" 947100319955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100320133","data":{"timestamp":" 947100320133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100320137","data":{"timestamp":" 947100320137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALI"," userResponse":" SWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100320141","data":{"timestamp":" 947100320141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100320148","data":{"timestamp":" 947100320147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100320854","data":{"timestamp":" 947100320854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMA"," userResponse":" MNYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100321448","data":{"timestamp":" 947100321447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMUONA"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100325496","data":{"timestamp":" 947100325496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMUONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100327779","data":{"timestamp":" 947100327779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100327963","data":{"timestamp":" 947100327962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100328497","data":{"timestamp":" 947100328497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100329878","data":{"timestamp":" 947100329877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100330476","data":{"timestamp":" 947100330474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100332461","data":{"timestamp":" 947100332461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100332765","data":{"timestamp":" 947100332764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100333362","data":{"timestamp":" 947100333362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100334502","data":{"timestamp":" 947100334502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100335201","data":{"timestamp":" 947100335201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100336600","data":{"timestamp":" 947100336600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100337060","data":{"timestamp":" 947100337060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100337568","data":{"timestamp":" 947100337568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100338034","data":{"timestamp":" 947100338034"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100338307","data":{"timestamp":" 947100338307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100339118","data":{"timestamp":" 947100339117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100341046","data":{"timestamp":" 947100341045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100341209","data":{"timestamp":" 947100341209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100341966","data":{"timestamp":" 947100341966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100343106","data":{"timestamp":" 947100343105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100344793","data":{"timestamp":" 947100344793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100345938","data":{"timestamp":" 947100345938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100347767","data":{"timestamp":" 947100347767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100348929","data":{"timestamp":" 947100348928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100349646","data":{"timestamp":" 947100349646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100351671","data":{"timestamp":" 947100351670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100352891","data":{"timestamp":" 947100352891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100353559","data":{"timestamp":" 947100353558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100354361","data":{"timestamp":" 947100354360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFARU"," userResponse":" KIFARU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100358926","data":{"timestamp":" 947100358926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100360503","data":{"timestamp":" 947100360503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100361319","data":{"timestamp":" 947100361318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100362781","data":{"timestamp":" 947100362781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIFARU"," userResponse":" START_KIFARU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100367117","data":{"timestamp":" 947100367117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFARU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100368871","data":{"timestamp":" 947100368870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100369100","data":{"timestamp":" 947100369099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100369575","data":{"timestamp":" 947100369575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100370048","data":{"timestamp":" 947100370048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMBE"," userResponse":" PEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100370653","data":{"timestamp":" 947100370653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100371078","data":{"timestamp":" 947100371078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100371542","data":{"timestamp":" 947100371542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100372999","data":{"timestamp":" 947100372998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOCHONGOKA"," userResponse":" ILIYOCHONGOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100373789","data":{"timestamp":" 947100373788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100376176","data":{"timestamp":" 947100376176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100376398","data":{"timestamp":" 947100376397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100376756","data":{"timestamp":" 947100376756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100376967","data":{"timestamp":" 947100376967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMBE"," userResponse":" PEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100378483","data":{"timestamp":" 947100378483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100380905","data":{"timestamp":" 947100380905"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100383319","data":{"timestamp":" 947100383319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100383639","data":{"timestamp":" 947100383638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100384310","data":{"timestamp":" 947100384310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOCHONGOKA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100385266","data":{"timestamp":" 947100385265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOCHONGOKA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100387108","data":{"timestamp":" 947100387108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOCHONGOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100387420","data":{"timestamp":" 947100387419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100388627","data":{"timestamp":" 947100388627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100390961","data":{"timestamp":" 947100390961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100391149","data":{"timestamp":" 947100391148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100391727","data":{"timestamp":" 947100391723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100392199","data":{"timestamp":" 947100392199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100393449","data":{"timestamp":" 947100393449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100394237","data":{"timestamp":" 947100394236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100394968","data":{"timestamp":" 947100394968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100395554","data":{"timestamp":" 947100395554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100395929","data":{"timestamp":" 947100395929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100396415","data":{"timestamp":" 947100396414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100397399","data":{"timestamp":" 947100397398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100405615","data":{"timestamp":" 947100405615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100406495","data":{"timestamp":" 947100406495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100406876","data":{"timestamp":" 947100406876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100407389","data":{"timestamp":" 947100407389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100409398","data":{"timestamp":" 947100409398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100409809","data":{"timestamp":" 947100409808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" START_KIBOKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100412254","data":{"timestamp":" 947100412254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100413660","data":{"timestamp":" 947100413660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100413969","data":{"timestamp":" 947100413968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100414274","data":{"timestamp":" 947100414274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100415366","data":{"timestamp":" 947100415366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100416153","data":{"timestamp":" 947100416152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100418399","data":{"timestamp":" 947100418399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100418883","data":{"timestamp":" 947100418883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100419377","data":{"timestamp":" 947100419377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100420370","data":{"timestamp":" 947100420370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKULA"," userResponse":" UNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100421232","data":{"timestamp":" 947100421232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100423423","data":{"timestamp":" 947100423423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100423815","data":{"timestamp":" 947100423815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100424531","data":{"timestamp":" 947100424530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100425406","data":{"timestamp":" 947100425406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKULA"," userResponse":" UNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100425510","data":{"timestamp":" 947100425510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100427933","data":{"timestamp":" 947100427933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100428507","data":{"timestamp":" 947100428506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100430960","data":{"timestamp":" 947100430960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100431656","data":{"timestamp":" 947100431656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100434197","data":{"timestamp":" 947100434197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANANGU"," userResponse":" MWANANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100435596","data":{"timestamp":" 947100435596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIULIZE"," userResponse":" USIULIZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100436228","data":{"timestamp":" 947100436228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100436936","data":{"timestamp":" 947100436935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100437380","data":{"timestamp":" 947100437379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100437904","data":{"timestamp":" 947100437904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100438558","data":{"timestamp":" 947100438558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100439024","data":{"timestamp":" 947100439024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100440108","data":{"timestamp":" 947100440107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100448602","data":{"timestamp":" 947100448602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100450608","data":{"timestamp":" 947100450608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USIULIZE"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100452594","data":{"timestamp":" 947100452594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIULIZE"," userResponse":" USIULIZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100454002","data":{"timestamp":" 947100454002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100454793","data":{"timestamp":" 947100454793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100455409","data":{"timestamp":" 947100455408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100455738","data":{"timestamp":" 947100455738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100456518","data":{"timestamp":" 947100456518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100457751","data":{"timestamp":" 947100457751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100459289","data":{"timestamp":" 947100459289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100460747","data":{"timestamp":" 947100460747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100462746","data":{"timestamp":" 947100462745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100465102","data":{"timestamp":" 947100465102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100465777","data":{"timestamp":" 947100465777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100466750","data":{"timestamp":" 947100466750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANUNA"," userResponse":" KANUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100467195","data":{"timestamp":" 947100467195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100467676","data":{"timestamp":" 947100467676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100468470","data":{"timestamp":" 947100468469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100470637","data":{"timestamp":" 947100470637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100472051","data":{"timestamp":" 947100472051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100473908","data":{"timestamp":" 947100473908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100475521","data":{"timestamp":" 947100475521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" KANUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100476457","data":{"timestamp":" 947100476457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100478116","data":{"timestamp":" 947100478115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100482532","data":{"timestamp":" 947100482532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KANUNA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100483492","data":{"timestamp":" 947100483492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANUNA"," userResponse":" KANUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100484655","data":{"timestamp":" 947100484655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100486220","data":{"timestamp":" 947100486219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100486682","data":{"timestamp":" 947100486682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100488877","data":{"timestamp":" 947100488877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100491261","data":{"timestamp":" 947100491261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100491895","data":{"timestamp":" 947100491894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100492546","data":{"timestamp":" 947100492546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100493455","data":{"timestamp":" 947100493455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100494271","data":{"timestamp":" 947100494270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100495400","data":{"timestamp":" 947100495400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUATE"," userResponse":" NIFUATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100495951","data":{"timestamp":" 947100495950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100496685","data":{"timestamp":" 947100496685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100498757","data":{"timestamp":" 947100498757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100500445","data":{"timestamp":" 947100500445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100500576","data":{"timestamp":" 947100500576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" START_MWEREVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100501601","data":{"timestamp":" 947100501601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100503235","data":{"timestamp":" 947100503231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100504827","data":{"timestamp":" 947100504827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100505949","data":{"timestamp":" 947100505949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100506918","data":{"timestamp":" 947100506918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" NIFUATE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100512102","data":{"timestamp":" 947100512101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100514530","data":{"timestamp":" 947100514530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUATE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100515789","data":{"timestamp":" 947100515789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100516699","data":{"timestamp":" 947100516699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100518679","data":{"timestamp":" 947100518679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100519412","data":{"timestamp":" 947100519412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAONA"," userResponse":" UTAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100520226","data":{"timestamp":" 947100520226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBACHO"," userResponse":" AMBACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100520840","data":{"timestamp":" 947100520840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100521394","data":{"timestamp":" 947100521394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100522197","data":{"timestamp":" 947100522197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100525548","data":{"timestamp":" 947100525547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100527440","data":{"timestamp":" 947100527440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100530172","data":{"timestamp":" 947100530172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBACHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100538756","data":{"timestamp":" 947100538756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100542721","data":{"timestamp":" 947100542721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100544721","data":{"timestamp":" 947100544721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100546995","data":{"timestamp":" 947100546995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100547160","data":{"timestamp":" 947100547160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100547734","data":{"timestamp":" 947100547734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100548818","data":{"timestamp":" 947100548818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" ALIMFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100549671","data":{"timestamp":" 947100549671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100550185","data":{"timestamp":" 947100550185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100550928","data":{"timestamp":" 947100550928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100553789","data":{"timestamp":" 947100553789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100555591","data":{"timestamp":" 947100555590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100558179","data":{"timestamp":" 947100558179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100560551","data":{"timestamp":" 947100560550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100562683","data":{"timestamp":" 947100562683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100564714","data":{"timestamp":" 947100564714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100567613","data":{"timestamp":" 947100567613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100570968","data":{"timestamp":" 947100570967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPENYEZA"," userResponse":" ALIJIPENYEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100571462","data":{"timestamp":" 947100571462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100572476","data":{"timestamp":" 947100572476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIANZI"," userResponse":" MIANZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100572983","data":{"timestamp":" 947100572981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100573902","data":{"timestamp":" 947100573902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" KUSIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100574381","data":{"timestamp":" 947100574380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100574925","data":{"timestamp":" 947100574925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINGO"," userResponse":" KINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100575129","data":{"timestamp":" 947100575129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100575653","data":{"timestamp":" 947100575653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100579103","data":{"timestamp":" 947100579102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPENYEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100581249","data":{"timestamp":" 947100581249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100583569","data":{"timestamp":" 947100583569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIANZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100590694","data":{"timestamp":" 947100590694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100595671","data":{"timestamp":" 947100595671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100597756","data":{"timestamp":" 947100597756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100599928","data":{"timestamp":" 947100599928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100602173","data":{"timestamp":" 947100602173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100603975","data":{"timestamp":" 947100603975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100606345","data":{"timestamp":" 947100606345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAZAMA"," userResponse":" ALITAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100607018","data":{"timestamp":" 947100607018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100607153","data":{"timestamp":" 947100607153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100607657","data":{"timestamp":" 947100607657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100607876","data":{"timestamp":" 947100607875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100608774","data":{"timestamp":" 947100608774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUULIZA"," userResponse":" KUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100609931","data":{"timestamp":" 947100609930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100610796","data":{"timestamp":" 947100610796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100611282","data":{"timestamp":" 947100611282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUKO"," userResponse":" YUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100612366","data":{"timestamp":" 947100612365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100615427","data":{"timestamp":" 947100615426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAZAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100617829","data":{"timestamp":" 947100617829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100620668","data":{"timestamp":" 947100620668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100622941","data":{"timestamp":" 947100622941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100624971","data":{"timestamp":" 947100624971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100630848","data":{"timestamp":" 947100630848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100633813","data":{"timestamp":" 947100633813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100638960","data":{"timestamp":" 947100638960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100640804","data":{"timestamp":" 947100640803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100643245","data":{"timestamp":" 947100643245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100645978","data":{"timestamp":" 947100645978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HABARI"," userResponse":" HABARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100646715","data":{"timestamp":" 947100646714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100647645","data":{"timestamp":" 947100647645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100648097","data":{"timestamp":" 947100648096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100648721","data":{"timestamp":" 947100648721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100648955","data":{"timestamp":" 947100648955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100649418","data":{"timestamp":" 947100649418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100652425","data":{"timestamp":" 947100652425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HABARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100654687","data":{"timestamp":" 947100654686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100663053","data":{"timestamp":" 947100663053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100665922","data":{"timestamp":" 947100665922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100669071","data":{"timestamp":" 947100669071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100681201","data":{"timestamp":" 947100681201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100694159","data":{"timestamp":" 947100694159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100696052","data":{"timestamp":" 947100696051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HABARI"," userResponse":" HABARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100696280","data":{"timestamp":" 947100696279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100696973","data":{"timestamp":" 947100696972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100697854","data":{"timestamp":" 947100697853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100698422","data":{"timestamp":" 947100698422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100698663","data":{"timestamp":" 947100698663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100699367","data":{"timestamp":" 947100699367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100700305","data":{"timestamp":" 947100700305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100701312","data":{"timestamp":" 947100701312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100706480","data":{"timestamp":" 947100706480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HABARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100719306","data":{"timestamp":" 947100719306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100722600","data":{"timestamp":" 947100722599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100725163","data":{"timestamp":" 947100725163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100727610","data":{"timestamp":" 947100727609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100729792","data":{"timestamp":" 947100729792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100732418","data":{"timestamp":" 947100732418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100735127","data":{"timestamp":" 947100735127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100737696","data":{"timestamp":" 947100737695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100739613","data":{"timestamp":" 947100739613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100740540","data":{"timestamp":" 947100740539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100741984","data":{"timestamp":" 947100741984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKANIELEZA"," userResponse":" UKANIELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100742858","data":{"timestamp":" 947100742858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100743322","data":{"timestamp":" 947100743322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100743946","data":{"timestamp":" 947100743946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100744406","data":{"timestamp":" 947100744406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100745350","data":{"timestamp":" 947100745350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100748970","data":{"timestamp":" 947100748970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100751639","data":{"timestamp":" 947100751639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100753711","data":{"timestamp":" 947100753711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKANIELEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100755687","data":{"timestamp":" 947100755687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100758373","data":{"timestamp":" 947100758373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100760430","data":{"timestamp":" 947100760429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100762386","data":{"timestamp":" 947100762386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100764740","data":{"timestamp":" 947100764740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100767151","data":{"timestamp":" 947100767150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAMA"," userResponse":" INAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100767877","data":{"timestamp":" 947100767877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100768481","data":{"timestamp":" 947100768481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100769584","data":{"timestamp":" 947100769584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100770078","data":{"timestamp":" 947100770078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100770471","data":{"timestamp":" 947100770471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100771076","data":{"timestamp":" 947100771076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100771640","data":{"timestamp":" 947100771639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100772774","data":{"timestamp":" 947100772774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100773230","data":{"timestamp":" 947100773230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100773633","data":{"timestamp":" 947100773633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100777247","data":{"timestamp":" 947100777247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100779218","data":{"timestamp":" 947100779217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100781780","data":{"timestamp":" 947100781780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100785058","data":{"timestamp":" 947100785058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKWAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100786941","data":{"timestamp":" 947100786941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100789010","data":{"timestamp":" 947100789009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100790959","data":{"timestamp":" 947100790959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100793317","data":{"timestamp":" 947100793317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100796955","data":{"timestamp":" 947100796955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100798897","data":{"timestamp":" 947100798897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100801296","data":{"timestamp":" 947100801295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100803114","data":{"timestamp":" 947100803113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100803248","data":{"timestamp":" 947100803248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100803771","data":{"timestamp":" 947100803770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100804900","data":{"timestamp":" 947100804898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINAMA"," userResponse":" ALIINAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100805534","data":{"timestamp":" 947100805534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100806221","data":{"timestamp":" 947100806221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100807100","data":{"timestamp":" 947100807100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100807703","data":{"timestamp":" 947100807703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100808146","data":{"timestamp":" 947100808146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100808582","data":{"timestamp":" 947100808582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100809340","data":{"timestamp":" 947100809340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100812833","data":{"timestamp":" 947100812832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100815732","data":{"timestamp":" 947100815732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100817623","data":{"timestamp":" 947100817623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100819927","data":{"timestamp":" 947100819926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100822395","data":{"timestamp":" 947100822395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100827533","data":{"timestamp":" 947100827533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100830856","data":{"timestamp":" 947100830856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100832901","data":{"timestamp":" 947100832901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100836450","data":{"timestamp":" 947100836450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100838850","data":{"timestamp":" 947100838850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100841021","data":{"timestamp":" 947100841020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100843234","data":{"timestamp":" 947100843233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100843486","data":{"timestamp":" 947100843486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100844196","data":{"timestamp":" 947100844196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100844463","data":{"timestamp":" 947100844463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100845026","data":{"timestamp":" 947100845025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100845967","data":{"timestamp":" 947100845967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100847131","data":{"timestamp":" 947100847131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWANI"," userResponse":" KUNYWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100847432","data":{"timestamp":" 947100847431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100848028","data":{"timestamp":" 947100848028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100851392","data":{"timestamp":" 947100851391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100853206","data":{"timestamp":" 947100853205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100857016","data":{"timestamp":" 947100857016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100862073","data":{"timestamp":" 947100862073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100864078","data":{"timestamp":" 947100864078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100869224","data":{"timestamp":" 947100869224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100869227","data":{"timestamp":" 947100869227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWANI"," userResponse":" KUNYWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100869926","data":{"timestamp":" 947100869926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100882290","data":{"timestamp":" 947100882290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100883444","data":{"timestamp":" 947100883444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100884016","data":{"timestamp":" 947100884016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100885099","data":{"timestamp":" 947100885099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKULA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100885151","data":{"timestamp":" 947100885151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" ATAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100885704","data":{"timestamp":" 947100885704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100886184","data":{"timestamp":" 947100886184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100886216","data":{"timestamp":" 947100886215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100886688","data":{"timestamp":" 947100886688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100887080","data":{"timestamp":" 947100887080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJANJA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100887344","data":{"timestamp":" 947100887344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMSHAWISHI"," userResponse":" MJANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100887764","data":{"timestamp":" 947100887764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" ALIYEMSHAWISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100888298","data":{"timestamp":" 947100888298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100888482","data":{"timestamp":" 947100888482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100888977","data":{"timestamp":" 947100888977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100889020","data":{"timestamp":" 947100889020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100930095","data":{"timestamp":" 947100930095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100930217","data":{"timestamp":" 947100930217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" fc0be5fc-374b-4978-a151-ab688e85003b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100938809","data":{"timestamp":" 947100938809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 637b2cd2-15f2-48af-ac5b-117832ffe1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100939038","data":{"timestamp":" 947100939038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 637b2cd2-15f2-48af-ac5b-117832ffe1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100940013","data":{"timestamp":" 947100940013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 637b2cd2-15f2-48af-ac5b-117832ffe1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100940452","data":{"timestamp":" 947100940452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 637b2cd2-15f2-48af-ac5b-117832ffe1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100940548","data":{"timestamp":" 947100940548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 637b2cd2-15f2-48af-ac5b-117832ffe1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947100952521","data":{"timestamp":" 947100952521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_215754"," gameId":" 637b2cd2-15f2-48af-ac5b-117832ffe1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}